http://www.iseekgolf.com/content/privacy-statement

Content | iSeekGolf.com
Close
FIND. BOOK. PLAY
Loading Courses
Search news for ""
Search the forum for ""
Sign In
Forgot password?
Sign Up
Loading Courses
Search news for ""
Search the forum for ""
Sign In
Forgot password?
Sign In
Forgot password?
Sign Up
Loading Courses
Search news for ""
Search the forum for ""
Privacy Statement
Micropower Pty Ltd ACN 007 336 736 (Micropower) has developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about how we deal with privacy issues in relation to our iseekgolf.com website.Collection of InformationMicropower collects your full name, email address and phone number each time you make a booking or payment with iseekgolf.com. We do not collect any credit card information nor store any credit card information.  Where we require payment from you, all payments are processed by an external payment provider in accordance with their own privacy policy.  Our payment provider is PaypalAdditionally, when you visit the iseekgolf.com website, our internet service provider can record certain information in relation to your visit such as:your internet address;your domain name;your internet service provider;the date and time of your visit to the website;the length of your session;the pages which you have accessed;the website which referred you to our website;the type and version of the browser you are using;the operating system which your computer uses.This information is only used for statistical and website development purposes, and cannot personally identify you;Various pages in this site invite you to email us your name and contact details, for example to become a member of iseekgolf.com and go onto our mailing list for our newsletter or to enter competitions or receive details for golf related services from our sponsors.If you use our forum, you are asked to provide your name and email address.Micropower will not otherwise collect information from you through this web site unless you knowingly provide it to us.We do use cookies, cookies enable us to tell when you use the website and also to help customise your website experience. Cookies can be deleted from you computer at any time; however this will remove all cookies from your computer, not just those in relation to iseekgolf.com.Use of InformationMicropower will only use the information it collects through this website for the following purposes:providing information to a service provider, for example, a golf course at which you have booked a tee time using iseekgolf.com;forwarding iseekgolf.com newsletters and other information such as details about golf related products and services from our sponsors;monitoring web site performance;improving our website and services to you;internal administration; andother purposes that are in accordance with your consent.Micropower will not give, sell, trade or otherwise disclose any personal information about you to a third party unless:it is in the course of the provision of services to you;you have provided us with your consent; orwe are required to do so by law.Access and CorrectionYou can ask us for access to your personal information.You can ask us to correct or update your personal information.Opt OutIf you no longer wish to receive communications from us, send us an email at info@iseekgolf.comLinks to Other SitesThis site may contain links to other sites. Micropower is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked sites, and does not represent that it has any endorsements, affiliations, sponsorships or approvals by reason of any links to other sites.SecurityIf you send us information from this site, it will be encrypted. We use industry-standard 128–bit encryption in place to protect information collected through this site.Further InformationFor further information about the privacy policy of iseekgolf.com and Micropower, please email us at info@iseekgolf.comCopyrightThe materials and content on this website (including text, documents, photographs, graphics and audio) are protected by copyright law. Micropower reserves all of its copyright and other intellectual property rights. Unless permitted under the Copyright Act 1968, no materials or content may be reproduced without permission. Please address any queries to info@iseekgolf.comContactMicropower's contact details are:Micropower Pty Ltd
17 Guthrie St
Paddington, QLD, 406
Regions
New South Wales
Queensland
Victoria
Australia Capital Territory
Tasmania
Forgot password?
Sign Up
Loading Courses
Search news for ""
Search the forum for ""
© 2000—2020 iseekgolf.com. All Rights Reserved. ABN: 87 007 336 736
Forgot password?
